themechilly.com 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy | ThemeChilly

## ThemeChilly Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains the method in which ThemeChilly collects, maintains and uses the personal information that you provide on our website- [ThemeChilly.com](http://www.themechilly.com/) when you use it. ThemeChilly commits to protect the privacy of its website users. Any specific information that you are asked to share while browsing this website will only be utilized as per this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to any third party.

ThemeChilly may modify this privacy statement from time to time. You are therefore advised to check this page to ensure that you remain updated with any changes in the privacy policy. This privacy policy is effective from December 25th, 2014.

## Collection & Usage of Personal Information

The following information may be collected from you: 

  * Contact Details, like name, email address, contact address, phone number.
  * In case you are registering on behalf of your organization, then your organizational details, like your organization's name, your job title, company's address, and other related information.
  * Billing Information which include payment mode and billing address.
  * Demographic details, like postcode, interests and preferences.
  * Also as with most other sites, we automatically collect some details about your computer, like your IP address, referring/exit pages, browser type etc.

## Why do we collect & what do we do with your information?

This information that we collect is utilized to understand your requirements in order to server you better. With the information that is collected, we: 

  * Maintain internal records.
  * Respond to service and offer requests.
  * Improve our services, products and marketing efforts.
  * Administering your account.
  * Send periodic promotional mails which we think may be of utility to you by using the email address provided by you.

## Information Security

ThemeChilly is committed to keep your personal information secure. In order to safeguard your information collected online from any unauthorized disclosure or access, we have leveraged proper electronic, managerial and physical procedures in place. We do not sell/transfer/share your personal information to any third party, except in case where the law or any legal procedure requires us to do so.

## Tracking cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use persistent cookie to store user ID and session cookie to store different master IDs. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers are not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

In all, cookies help us in serving you better. A cookie does not provides us access to any information about you, other than what you choose to share with us. You can accept or decline cookies if you prefer. But declining cookies may prevent you from taking complete advantage of the site.

## Links to other websites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of ThemeChilly. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by the privacy statements of those other websites. We advise you to carefully read the privacy statement of any web site you visit and if you share any of your information with these websites, it shall be deemed that you have carefully gone through their Privacy Policy and all other conditions on such other websites, the link of which is provided on our website, and having understood and accepted their conditions, you have shared your information for which we shall not be responsible in any manner. 

## Controlling your information

If you do not want us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may drop us a mail at [support@themechilly.com](mailto:support@themechilly.com).

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or emailing us at the address given below: ThemeChilly, D-10/52, Opp. Chitrakoot Stadium, Chitrakoot, Vaishali Nagar, Jaipur-21 (India) Email: [support@themechilly.com](mailto:support@themechilly.com)
